# Alejandro Meza

# SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING SPECIALIST

#### CONTACT

512-743-8896

Alejandro.meza@g.austincc.edu

# **SKILLS**

JavaScript/jQuery

Python

C++

Front end technologies

PHP

Fluent in Spanish

Microsoft Office

Computer Hardware

Data Structures & Algorithms

# **EDUCATION**

Austin Community College

## 2023-2024

Associate's in computer Programming

University of Texas at Austin

2021-2023

**Economics** 

#### **PROFILE**

Computer programmer with experience gained through schooling and personal projects. Most of my work comes from front and back-end development as well as a deep understanding of object-oriented programming. My goal is to create clean, useful, and efficient programs with the knowledge I've gained through schooling. At the same time learn as much as possible from my peers, company, and environment.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Tesla - Production Associate

## 2024

Clean and inspect parts for production vehicles. Tasked with inspecting parts sent to other areas of the factory. Replaced the tooling on the machines and programmed the machine for the next run while ensuring equipment was clean and in optimal condition.

Target-Front Sales Associate

# 2022-2024

Ran and operated the self-checkout and registers while ensuring all check lane team members got their breaks.

Collected money from all registers at the end of the night.

Ran the customer service counter ensuring all customer returns and drive up orders were fulfilled. Prepare orders that were placed online. Restock of products on shelves. All work done with little to no supervision

J&J Remodeling

# 2021-2022

Prepared the work area for remodeling. Pick up, transport, and prepare the materials for the project at hand. Pick up and drop off workers for the shift. Translate English to Spanish for the boss and workers.